[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Married twice, divorced twice, what the hell does he know about it?", "question_tokens": ["Married", "twice", ",", "divorced", "twice", ",", "what", "the", "hell", "does", "he", "know", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "VBD", "NN", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "Just because a marriage doesn't last forever doesn't mean it's a failure.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "because", "a", "marriage", "does", "n't", "last", "forever", "does", "n't", "mean", "it", "'s", "a", "failure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "Do you have a secret admirer, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "secret", "admirer", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "Phaedra Parks.", "answer_tokens": ["Phaedra", "Parks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kandi Burruss"]}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "So who has time for romance?", "question_tokens": ["So", "who", "has", "time", "for", "romance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "Kandi Burruss.", "answer_tokens": ["Kandi", "Burruss", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "Donny Deutsch, you've been married and divorced twice, what do you think gives you the possible right to now put yourself up there as Mr. Love Guru expert to the nation's women?", "question_tokens": ["Donny", "Deutsch", ",", "you", "'ve", "been", "married", "and", "divorced", "twice", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "gives", "you", "the", "possible", "right", "to", "now", "put", "yourself", "up", "there", "as", "Mr.", "Love", "Guru", "expert", "to", "the", "nation", "'s", "women", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "EX", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "Jump right into it.", "answer_tokens": ["Jump", "right", "into", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donny Deutsch", "Mr. Love"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "Are you reformed character?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "reformed", "character", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "One of them is 24 years old?", "question_tokens": ["One", "of", "them", "is", "24", "years", "old", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "And the other ones are 3 and 7.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "the", "other", "ones", "are", "3", "and", "7", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "You just changed or?", "question_tokens": ["You", "just", "changed", "or", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "I think that it's a combination of age, it's a combination of mistakes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "a", "combination", "of", "age", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "combination", "of", "mistakes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Are men romantic really?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "men", "romantic", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "I don't think men by nature are what I call romantic.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "men", "by", "nature", "are", "what", "I", "call", "romantic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Does she like football?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "she", "like", "football", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "She loves football.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "loves", "football", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Here's why.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "why", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Are you a fine human being?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "fine", "human", "being", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "I'm flawed but I think very funny.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "flawed", "but", "I", "think", "very", "funny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 147, "question": "What are the flaws?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "flaws", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "The flaws --", "answer_tokens": ["The", "flaws", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Do we have an hour?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "have", "an", "hour", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Maybe because where I was in my career, I think the third time will be the charm for me.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "because", "where", "I", "was", "in", "my", "career", ",", "I", "think", "the", "third", "time", "will", "be", "the", "charm", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "You think you will get remarried again?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "you", "will", "get", "remarried", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "EUTSCH: I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["EUTSCH", ":", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Third time?", "question_tokens": ["Third", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "You've been married twice, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "been", "married", "twice", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "When you look back on it, what have you learned?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", "on", "it", ",", "what", "have", "you", "learned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "I was married to two great women.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "married", "to", "two", "great", "women", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "NNP", ":", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "And you ask yourselves together, should we renew this contract, this business arrangement we have?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "ask", "yourselves", "together", ",", "should", "we", "renew", "this", "contract", ",", "this", "business", "arrangement", "we", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "EUTSCH: I must say (INAUDIBLE), but I do think like in anything, in a business relationship, in a friendship, in any type of a partnership, it's not unconditional.", "answer_tokens": ["EUTSCH", ":", "I", "must", "say", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", ",", "but", "I", "do", "think", "like", "in", "anything", ",", "in", "a", "business", "relationship", ",", "in", "a", "friendship", ",", "in", "any", "type", "of", "a", "partnership", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "unconditional", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Do you believe that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Do you believe that (INAUDIBLE) change their spots?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "change", "their", "spots", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Are women taking this seriously so far?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "women", "taking", "this", "seriously", "so", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "-- are believing you're some sort of love guru?", "question_tokens": ["--", "are", "believing", "you", "'re", "some", "sort", "of", "love", "guru", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "And you refer to things as what?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "refer", "to", "things", "as", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Yes, it's like, just get over right.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "like", ",", "just", "get", "over", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "You can't say that with a straight face, can you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "ca", "n't", "say", "that", "with", "a", "straight", "face", ",", "can", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "I can't really.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "OK?", "question_tokens": ["OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York", "America"]}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Everybody's got something, right?", "question_tokens": ["Everybody", "'s", "got", "something", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "As a powerful ad man, you know, one of the top executives in New York and you've seen how America has gone through a very tough period.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "a", "powerful", "ad", "man", ",", "you", "know", ",", "one", "of", "the", "top", "executives", "in", "New", "York", "and", "you", "'ve", "seen", "how", "America", "has", "gone", "through", "a", "very", "tough", "period", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "What would you do to get America back on its feet?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "do", "to", "get", "America", "back", "on", "its", "feet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "I think what I would do, and I know this is not going to be a popular answer.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "what", "I", "would", "do", ",", "and", "I", "know", "this", "is", "not", "going", "to", "be", "a", "popular", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "But isn't the answer really to do business with them?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "n't", "the", "answer", "really", "to", "do", "business", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Well, if you look at the history of the world there needs to be a check and balance.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "you", "look", "at", "the", "history", "of", "the", "world", "there", "needs", "to", "be", "a", "check", "and", "balance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "What is your assessment of her as a potential challenger to the White House?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "assessment", "of", "her", "as", "a", "potential", "challenger", "to", "the", "White", "House", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "She's unelectable.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "unelectable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "Is every brand rescuable?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "every", "brand", "rescuable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "I mean, it's Lindsay Lohan right now, if you were able to rebrand her, you could rescue her?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "Lindsay", "Lohan", "right", "now", ",", "if", "you", "were", "able", "to", "rebrand", "her", ",", "you", "could", "rescue", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "She's waiting to happen.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "waiting", "to", "happen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lindsay Lohan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Vick"]}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "NN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Who is not rescuable?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "not", "rescuable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Somebody that commits a horrible act to children or somebody that murders, or someone -- we even saw Michael Vick, you know, who did an almost horrific, horrific thing, and what he did with these dogs.", "answer_tokens": ["Somebody", "that", "commits", "a", "horrible", "act", "to", "children", "or", "somebody", "that", "murders", ",", "or", "someone", "--", "we", "even", "saw", "Michael", "Vick", ",", "you", "know", ",", "who", "did", "an", "almost", "horrific", ",", "horrific", "thing", ",", "and", "what", "he", "did", "with", "these", "dogs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Which has been the biggest aphrodisiac to women?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "has", "been", "the", "biggest", "aphrodisiac", "to", "women", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Power, no question.", "answer_tokens": ["Power", ",", "no", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 470, "question": "How appealing do you think you are to women?", "question_tokens": ["How", "appealing", "do", "you", "think", "you", "are", "to", "women", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBG", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "I think --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "NN", ",", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "And I want any control -- I want to play back how many times you said rich, handsome, powerful -- what were the other ones?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "want", "any", "control", "--", "I", "want", "to", "play", "back", "how", "many", "times", "you", "said", "rich", ",", "handsome", ",", "powerful", "--", "what", "were", "the", "other", "ones", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "NN", ",", "JJ", ":", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Rich, handsome, powerful and a big house.", "answer_tokens": ["Rich", ",", "handsome", ",", "powerful", "and", "a", "big", "house", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donny"]}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ":", "PRP$", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Hello, great, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Hello", ",", "great", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Before we go any further, ladies, I want you to respond immediately to Donny's claims -- his two claims, really.", "answer_tokens": ["Before", "we", "go", "any", "further", ",", "ladies", ",", "I", "want", "you", "to", "respond", "immediately", "to", "Donny", "'s", "claims", "--", "his", "two", "claims", ",", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "What is your instant reaction?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "instant", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "I would have to say I do like a bit of a bad boy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "have", "to", "say", "I", "do", "like", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "bad", "boy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Do you know now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Mm-hmm.", "answer_tokens": ["Mm-hmm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Is he the kind of guy a woman would go to for genuine advice about her difficulties with a man?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "the", "kind", "of", "guy", "a", "woman", "would", "go", "to", "for", "genuine", "advice", "about", "her", "difficulties", "with", "a", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "I would think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Would you?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "I'm not sure.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Would you look at him now, with this cheeky grin, the twinkle in the eye, and think I reckon he's about to settle down seriously?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "look", "at", "him", "now", ",", "with", "this", "cheeky", "grin", ",", "the", "twinkle", "in", "the", "eye", ",", "and", "think", "I", "reckon", "he", "'s", "about", "to", "settle", "down", "seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "I didn't say about to.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "say", "about", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Ladies, we are ticking all the boxes here, aren't we?", "question_tokens": ["Ladies", ",", "we", "are", "ticking", "all", "the", "boxes", "here", ",", "are", "n't", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "You don't?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Are you going to get divorced, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "get", "divorced", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "It's possible.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "possible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Why has it come to this, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "has", "it", "come", "to", "this", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "Just a lot of things that have happened in our marriage over the years.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "a", "lot", "of", "things", "that", "have", "happened", "in", "our", "marriage", "over", "the", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "CC", "EX", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "A bad boy?", "question_tokens": ["A", "bad", "boy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "He has been a bad boy, here and there, over the years.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "has", "been", "a", "bad", "boy", ",", "here", "and", "there", ",", "over", "the", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Let's bring in the gurus.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "bring", "in", "the", "gurus", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "What would you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "I don't think there should be any secrets.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "should", "be", "any", "secrets", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Do you want to share the rest of your life with him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "share", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "life", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "Bryce and Brent, right?", "question_tokens": ["Bryce", "and", "Brent", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "When you have kids -- you've got three kids -- how much more difficult is it to simply say this marriage is over, move on, when there are kids involved?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "have", "kids", "--", "you", "'ve", "got", "three", "kids", "--", "how", "much", "more", "difficult", "is", "it", "to", "simply", "say", "this", "marriage", "is", "over", ",", "move", "on", ",", "when", "there", "are", "kids", "involved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "RBR", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "NN", "IN", ",", "WRB", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "Very difficult.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "difficult", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "Doesn't it eventually erode trust?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "it", "eventually", "erode", "trust", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "Yeah, it would.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "it", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "From what you've heard, what should she do?", "question_tokens": ["From", "what", "you", "'ve", "heard", ",", "what", "should", "she", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "She should follow her heart.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "should", "follow", "her", "heart", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "Because every guy that you go out with, you're thinking would he be a good step dad?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "every", "guy", "that", "you", "go", "out", "with", ",", "you", "'re", "thinking", "would", "he", "be", "a", "good", "step", "dad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "That's who I am, you know?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "who", "I", "am", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "Are you dating?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "dating", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "It's cool, but I know you don't -- I don't know if you watch our show.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "cool", ",", "but", "I", "know", "you", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "you", "watch", "our", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "If you are being self-critical, how much has been your fault and how much has been the guy's fault?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "are", "being", "self-critical", ",", "how", "much", "has", "been", "your", "fault", "and", "how", "much", "has", "been", "the", "guy", "'s", "fault", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "It depends.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "depends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 715, "question": "Or is it great sex?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "it", "great", "sex", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 716, "answer": "I think it has something to do with where they are in their life curve, frankly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "has", "something", "to", "do", "with", "where", "they", "are", "in", "their", "life", "curve", ",", "frankly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 725, "question": "Is he right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 730, "question": "Isn't passion key here, ladies?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "passion", "key", "here", ",", "ladies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "NN", "JJ", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "Yes, definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "Why are you happily married, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "happily", "married", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "I guess because I'm committed to the marriage.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "guess", "because", "I", "'m", "committed", "to", "the", "marriage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 745, "question": "What do you think now when you hear that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "now", "when", "you", "hear", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 746, "answer": "I think that's so brilliant, because you have a great business strategy about your marriage.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "so", "brilliant", ",", "because", "you", "have", "a", "great", "business", "strategy", "about", "your", "marriage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 757, "question": "Yes or no?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "or", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "Yes, I think I would.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "I", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "How can we help you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "we", "help", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "Well, I have a question.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "a", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 798, "question": "What's your view, Lauren?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "view", ",", "Lauren", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 799, "answer": "Now I think he's right.", "answer_tokens": ["Now", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lauren"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 815, "question": "I was wondering what are your top tips for keeping your partner happy in a relationship?", "question_tokens": ["I", "was", "wondering", "what", "are", "your", "top", "tips", "for", "keeping", "your", "partner", "happy", "in", "a", "relationship", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 816, "answer": "It's interesting.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "interesting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 840, "question": "Why don't he try something new?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "he", "try", "something", "new", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 841, "answer": "I didn't say all the time try -- he should.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "say", "all", "the", "time", "try", "--", "he", "should", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 844, "question": "Is it going to grow?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "going", "to", "grow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 845, "answer": "Love guru doesn't have an answer to that one.", "answer_tokens": ["Love", "guru", "does", "n't", "have", "an", "answer", "to", "that", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 852, "question": "What's your question?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "question", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 853, "answer": "Hi, everyone.", "answer_tokens": ["Hi", ",", "everyone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 858, "question": "I want to know she like better, Piers or Anderson Cooper?", "question_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "know", "she", "like", "better", ",", "Piers", "or", "Anderson", "Cooper", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJR", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 859, "answer": "Oh, I love that question.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "love", "that", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson Cooper"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson"]}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 860, "question": "Let's get that one out of the way first?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "get", "that", "one", "out", "of", "the", "way", "first", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 861, "answer": "I love Anderson.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "Anderson", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 866, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 867, "answer": "I'm sorry.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sorry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 871, "question": "Do you know what you're doing tonight?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "what", "you", "'re", "doing", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 872, "answer": "I'm not quite sure, but it will be something sexy and romantic with my husband.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "quite", "sure", ",", "but", "it", "will", "be", "something", "sexy", "and", "romantic", "with", "my", "husband", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 875, "question": "Where will you be tonight?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "will", "you", "be", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 876, "answer": "I'm not dating anybody, so I'll just be with myself.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "dating", "anybody", ",", "so", "I", "'ll", "just", "be", "with", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 877, "question": "Footloose and fancy free in New York?", "question_tokens": ["Footloose", "and", "fancy", "free", "in", "New", "York", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 878, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 881, "question": "Mimi, what are you doing?", "question_tokens": ["Mimi", ",", "what", "are", "you", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 882, "answer": "I'm free as a bird.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "free", "as", "a", "bird", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 885, "question": "Donnie, you in?", "question_tokens": ["Donnie", ",", "you", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 886, "answer": "I'm in.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 894, "question": "Why do you have to be romantic on this day?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "have", "to", "be", "romantic", "on", "this", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 895, "answer": "I think every woman wants to feel special.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "every", "woman", "wants", "to", "feel", "special", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 897, "question": "So it's important to you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "it", "'s", "important", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 898, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 901, "question": "For all three of you, this is a big day?", "question_tokens": ["For", "all", "three", "of", "you", ",", "this", "is", "a", "big", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 902, "answer": "All the holidays are a big day to me.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "the", "holidays", "are", "a", "big", "day", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "JJR", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 904, "question": "She's in New York, any advice?", "question_tokens": ["She", "'s", "in", "New", "York", ",", "any", "advice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 905, "answer": "Well, she better walk Wall Street.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "she", "better", "walk", "Wall", "Street", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "PRP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 908, "question": "Where are you going to be?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "going", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 909, "answer": "One of you producers asked me the same question.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "you", "producers", "asked", "me", "the", "same", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 918, "question": "The men should come to you, shouldn't they?", "question_tokens": ["The", "men", "should", "come", "to", "you", ",", "should", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 919, "answer": "I think they should find you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "should", "find", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 926, "question": "Could you go out with a poor guy?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "go", "out", "with", "a", "poor", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 927, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 932, "question": "Could you go out with a poor guy now?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "go", "out", "with", "a", "poor", "guy", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 933, "answer": "He can't be totally poor, because I don't want to take care.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "ca", "n't", "be", "totally", "poor", ",", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "take", "care", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 935, "question": "So they have to be wealthy?", "question_tokens": ["So", "they", "have", "to", "be", "wealthy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 936, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 946, "question": "You can take me, Donnie or Anderson Cooper?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "take", "me", ",", "Donnie", "or", "Anderson", "Cooper", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 947, "answer": "I'm taking you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "taking", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donnie", "Anderson Cooper"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson Cooper", "Donnie Deutsch"]}, "docId": "110214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 949, "question": "Wait, say that again?", "question_tokens": ["Wait", ",", "say", "that", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 950, "answer": "Desert island, rest of your life, me, Anderson Cooper, Donnie Deutsch.", "answer_tokens": ["Desert", "island", ",", "rest", "of", "your", "life", ",", "me", ",", "Anderson", "Cooper", ",", "Donnie", "Deutsch", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]